♪No matter how far the distance is, don’t be afraid♪
♪아무리 떨어져 있어도 두려워하지 마세요♪
♪Love is gentle and caring♪
♪사랑은 부드럽고 걱정으로 가득 차 있습니다♪
♪Those scars will always heal♪
♪그 상처는 언제나 아물 거야♪
♪They will come together like the flowers of time♪
♪그들은 시간의 꽃처럼 모일 것이다♪
♪Someone will eventually collect them for you♪
♪그리고 결국 누군가가 당신을 위해 그것들을 수집할 것입니다♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 가세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닐 거예요♪
♪Conversation with time♪
♪시간과 대화하세요♪
♪When the light falls softly, think of it as the answer♪
♪빛이 은은하게 내리면 대답으로 받아들이세요♪
♪May you find someone in the vast sea of ​​people♪
♪ 그 넓은 사람의 바다에서 누군가를 찾길 ♪
♪Take a cup of tea and be happy♪
♪가벼운 차를 즐기며 행복해요♪
♪Understand that life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있다는 것을 이해 ♪
♪There is still love♪
♪그래도 사랑해요♪
♪Winter and summer♪
♪겨울과 여름♪
【Love is a panacea】 【Episode 6】
[사랑은 만병통치약] [6화]
[Works funded by major art projects in Sichuan Province in 2022]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 주요 예술 프로젝트 지원 작품 ]
[Adapted from Meng Yuyan’s novel "Healing"]
[레몬 위얀의 소설 '힐링'을 각색함 ]
Finally, I finally had this.
드디어 이걸 먹을 수 있게 되었습니다.
How delicious.
정말 맛있다.
Wei An, why don’t you eat?
웨이안 씨, 왜 먹지 않나요?
The surgery was a success.
수술은 성공적이었습니다.
The general is already awake.
장군은 이미 깨어났습니다.
We are finally safe.
우리는 마침내 안전해졌습니다.
We were released.
우리는 석방되었습니다.
Let's celebrate!
축하하자!
let's go.
갑시다.
Now is not the time to celebrate.
지금은 축하할 때가 아니다.
We don't have the biopsy results yet.
아직 생체검사 결과가 없습니다.
the general said
장군님이 말씀하셨어요
Who is not afraid of death?
죽음을 두려워하지 않는 사람,
He knows nothing but is afraid of death.
그는 아무것도 이해하지 못한 채 죽는 것만을 두려워합니다.
Moreover, Dr. Gu has found the general's enemy.
게다가 구 박사는 이미 장군의 적을 찾아냈습니다.
Let us drink another toast to Dr. Gu.
다시 한 번 구박사님을 위해 건배합시다.
Thanks.
그라시아스.
You have worked hard.
당신은 열심히 일했습니다.
wait.
기다리다.
Why don't any of you drink? I'm the only one drinking.
왜 술 안 마시는 사람 있어? 나만 마시고 있어요.
My boss says alcohol paralyzes the central nervous system.
내 상사는 술이 중추신경계를 마비시킨다고 말했습니다 .
And affect the accuracy of surgery.
수술의 정밀도에 영향을 미칩니다.
Wei An, why don’t you have a drink too?
웨이안 씨, 당신도 술을 마시지 않겠습니까?
You don't need surgery.
수술을 할 필요는 없습니다.
She doesn't need surgery, but she should consider it
수술을 할 필요는 없지만 다음 사항도 고려해야 합니다.
Potential risk of brain shrinkage caused by alcohol.
알코올로 인한 뇌 위축의 잠재적 위험 .
arts.
Ven.
Eating shrimp can nourish the brain.
뇌에 영양을 공급하려면 새우를 먹어보세요.
You end up with brain atrophy.
당신은 뇌 위축으로 끝날 것입니다.
You don't drink because your resistance to alcohol is low.
당신은 술에 대한 저항력이 거의 없기 때문에 술을 마시지 않습니다.
After one drink, you will become drunk.
한 잔 마시고 나면 취하게 됩니다.
can you see it?
당신은 그것을 볼 수 있습니까?
Let's drink.
마시자.
Come on, let's have a drink.
자, 마시자.
You don't need to finish your drink.
음료를 다 마칠 필요는 없습니다.
[Evidence Department] I drank all the wine.
[증거부] 술을 다 마셨어요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
I see.
이해합니다.
Biopsy results are ready.
생체검사 결과가 준비되었습니다.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
our team
우리 팀
A very important battle was won.
매우 중요한 전투에서 승리했습니다.
Thanks.
그라시아스.
Average.
일반적인.
The surgery was a success.
수술은 성공적이었습니다.
But the battle was not won.
하지만 이 전투는 승리하지 못했습니다.
Biopsy results show
생검 결과 표시
Tumors are more malignant.
종양의 악성도가 높습니다.
Although all affected tissue was removed,
영향을 받은 조직이 모두 제거되었음에도 불구하고,
The recurrence rate of malignant tumors is very high.
악성 종양의 재발률은 매우 높습니다.
How long can I live?
내 앞으로 얼마나 살 수 있을까?
It depends on the rate of progress.
진행 속도에 따라 다릅니다.
possible
그럴 수도 있지
half a year,
반년,
But not more than two years.
하지만 2년을 넘기지 마세요.
No one can be invincible forever.
누구도 영원히 무적일 수는 없습니다.
Thank you
고마워
Let me know who I'm up against.
내 라이벌이 누구인지 보여줘서.
Sue, are you sad?
수야, 슬프니?
Are you still worried about not being able to charge for my wine?
술값을 청구할 수 없어서 걱정되시나요?
You are like Grandet.
당신은 그란데와 같습니다.
I'll make sure you make enough money soon.
곧 충분한 돈을 벌 수 있도록 할게요 .
Next month, come to my house for a New Year's party.
다음 달에는 집에서 열리는 신년 파티에 오세요.
We would get drunk together.
우리는 함께 취하겠습니다.
So, look,
그러니까 보세요,
We would drink lots and lots of wine.
우리는 술을 많이 마실 것입니다.
You will make a lot of money.
당신은 많은 돈을 벌게 될 것입니다.
Jiang, are you finished?
장, 끝났어?
immediately.
곧.
Come on, don't be late.
서둘러, 늦지 말자.
Otherwise the general will be angry.
그렇지 않으면 장군이 화를 낼 것입니다.
OK
좋아요.
I have found it.
나는 그것을 이미 찾았습니다.
What's this?
이게 뭔가요?
My lucky charm.
나의 행운의 부적.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I'm looking at the stars
나는 별을 바라보았다
And interpret my destiny.
그리고 내 운명을 읽어보세요.
Tonight, Venus is overhead.
오늘밤 금성은 머리 위에 있습니다.
The stars align in the house of love.
별들은 사랑의 집에 정렬됩니다.
Love rating is five stars.
애정도는 별 다섯개 입니다.
And this night,
그리고 오늘 밤,
I'm going to meet my prince.
나는 나의 왕자님을 만나러 갈 거예요.
I was so excited thinking about this.
나는 그것에 대해 매우 감정적으로 생각합니다.
What does this have to do with your amulet?
그리고 그것이 당신의 부적과 무슨 관련이 있나요?
It has a lot to do with this.
그것은 그것과 많은 관련이 있습니다.
It will bring me good luck in love.
그것은 나에게 사랑의 행운을 가져다 줄 것입니다.
Jiang.
장.
all
모두
in your life
당신의 인생에서
There is a certain sense of ritual.
그것은 일종의 의식적인 분위기를 가지고 있습니다.
I heard there is a custom in Lakaya.
라카야에는 풍습이 있다고 들었습니다.
When the New Year's bell rings,
새해의 종이 울리면 ,
You kiss the people around you,
가까운 사람에게 키스를 하고,
And you will have good luck all year long.
그리고 당신은 일년 내내 행운을 누릴 것입니다 .
Do they have this custom?
그 사람들이 그런 관습을 갖고 있나요?
You read too many romance novels.
당신은 로맨스 소설을 너무 많이 읽었습니다.
Don't you believe it?
당신은 그것을 믿지 않습니까?
In Lakaya, you have to adapt to their customs.
라카야에서는 그들의 관습에 적응해야 합니다.
Even if Dr. Gu is by my side tonight ,
오늘 밤 구 박사가 내 곁에 있어도
I will kiss him.
나는 그에게 키스할 것이다.
do not regret.
후회하지 마세요.
I won't do it.
나는 그것을하지 않을 것입니다.
I don't have time to make other people like me.
다른 사람이 나를 좋아해줄 시간이 없어요 .
Okay, go get your hair done quickly.
알았어, 당장 가서 머리를 다듬어라.
quickly! go.
빠른! 가다.
quickly!
빠른!
Wei'an.
웨이안.
You look beautiful today.
오늘 당신은 매우 아름다워 보입니다.
The date was stuck and he was strangling me.
데이트가 막혀서 그 사람이 나를 목을 졸라대고 있어요.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
You look handsome.
당신은 매우 잘생겼어요.
So when we get there I have to stay away from you,
그러니 우리가 그곳에 도착하면 나는 당신에게서 떨어져 있어야 할 것입니다.
Otherwise the girls won't see me.
그렇지 않으면 그 소녀들이 나를 볼 수 없을 것입니다.
Why haven't they come yet?
왜 아직 도착하지 않았나요?
We have been waiting for them for a long time.
우리는 그들을 오랫동안 기다려왔습니다.
Luxurious cars and beautiful women.
고급스러운 자동차와 아름다운 여인들.
It's worth the wait.
기다릴 만한 가치가 있을 것입니다.
Girls, get in the car.
얘들아, 차에 타라.
I want to go to the back seat.
뒷좌석에 타고 싶어요.
Fang Mingfan, you drive.
Fang Mingfan, 당신이 운전하세요.
Translator Jiang, sit in front.
장 번역가님, 앞에 앉으세요.
Why are you looking at me like this?
왜 나를 그렇게 보는 거죠?
Am I weird to you?
내가 이상한가요?
you
너
Don't you have a cold?
감기는 안 걸렸나요?
He has a handsome face but a clumsy mouth.
얼굴은 잘생겼지 만 입이 서툴다.
they are.
그들은.
You are more beautiful than the moon today.
오늘 당신은 달보다 더 아름답습니다.
Am I lucky enough to be your dance partner?
내가 당신의 댄스 파트너가 되는 영광을 누리고 있나요?
they are.
그들은.
I chatted with my mentor on the way.
가는 길에 선생님과 이야기를 나누고 있었습니다 .
Do you want to know what he said?
그가 무슨 말을 했는지 알고 싶나요?
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
When that expressionless guy
그 포커페이스의 그 남자가
Become a turkey with its feathers showing?
깃털을 드러낸 칠면조로 변했나요 ?
Let's talk in the car.
차 안에서 얘기하자.
You can't let him take Su Translator away.
그가 번역가 Su를 데려가게 할 수는 없습니다 .
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Won't you take me with you?
나도 데리고 가지 않을래?
I've never been in a sports car.
나는 스포츠카를 타본 적이 없습니다.
Translated by Jiang.
번역가 장.
You must sit next to me and be my navigator.
당신은 내 옆에 앉아 나의 길잡이가 되어 주어야 합니다 .
Although cell transplantation experiments
세포이식 실험을 하면서도
Because Huntington's disease has failed,
헌팅턴병이 실패했기 때문에
Dr. Marta never gave up.
마르타 박사는 결코 포기하지 않았습니다.
In fact, this experiment
실제로 이 실험은
Has been secretly restarted.
비밀리에 재부팅되었습니다.
Really?
정말?
have you solved it
이미 해결하셨나요?
A key step to improving survival rates?
생존율을 높이는 중요한 단계는 무엇입니까 ?
Does the new experiment involve transplanting your own cells?
새로운 실험에는 자신의 세포를 이식하는 것이 포함됩니까?
o Culture cells?
o 배양된 세포?
Has it entered the clinical stage?
이미 임상 단계인가요?
Have they started recruiting volunteers?
자원봉사자 모집을 시작했나요?
Take it easy.
그냥 쉬세요.
Your constant questions make me dizzy.
너의 끊임없는 질문이 나를 어지럽게 만든다.
they are.
그들은.
I thought you would be interested in this news.
나는 당신이 이 소식에 관심이 있을 것이라고 생각했습니다.
but i didn't expect
그런데 상상도 못했어요
You will know the details so well
당신이 세부 사항을 너무 잘 알고있을 것입니다
An experiment about a rare disease.
희귀병에 대한 실험입니다 .
they are.
그들은.
Talking about medicine so seriously
의학에 대해 너무 진지하게 이야기하세요.
Make you charming.
당신을 매력적으로 만듭니다.
I admire you more and more.
나는 당신을 점점 더 존경합니다.
Do I admire it?
나는 존경합니까?
No kidding.
농담 하지마.
I'm not kidding.
농담이 아냐.
You have a natural charm that you don't know you have.
당신은 자신도 모르는 자연스러운 매력을 갖고 있어요 .
among the crowd,
군중 한가운데서,
you always stand out
넌 항상 눈에 띄지
You will attract attention.
그리고 당신은 관심을 끌고 있습니다.
Look, he's looking at you.
보세요, 그 사람이 당신을 보고 있어요.
He's looking at you too.
그 사람도 당신을 보고 있어요.
So does he.
그도 마찬가지다.
Actually I wouldn't mind
사실 난 상관없어
Let her have more than one knight beside the princess.
공주 옆에 기사가 한 명 이상 있도록 해주세요 .
I'm not a princess,
나는 공주가 아니다.
I don't need a knight.
그리고 나는 기사가 필요하지 않습니다.
Boss, you are drinking to drown your sorrows here .
보스, 당신은 여기 슬픔을 술에 담그고 계십니다.
If you continue to drink,
계속 술을 마시면
Translator Su
번역가 수
He's really going to be with that peacock.
그 사람은 정말 그 공작새와 함께 갈 거예요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
(Gu Yunzheng, what’s wrong with you?)
(구윤정 씨, 무슨 일이에요?)
Dear guests, please pay attention.
주목하세요, 손님.
There are still ten minutes left until the New Year countdown.
새해 카운트다운까지 10분 남았습니다 .
When the bell rings,
종소리가 울리면,
let's hug and kiss
포옹하고 키스하자
Under fireworks.
불꽃놀이 아래서.
I am not wrong.
나는 틀리지 않았다.
But why are the celestial phenomena wrong?
그런데 왜 하늘의 징조가 잘못된 걸까요?
It's New Year's Eve
설날이에요
I will meet my prince.
내 왕자님을 만날 거라고.
But the day is almost over
하지만 하루가 거의 끝나가네요
And my prince has not come yet.
내 왕자는 아직 도착하지 않았어.
Jiang.
장.
I've been looking for you and here you are.
나는 당신을 찾고 있었는데 여기 있습니다.
【Daily Love Luck】
[일상적인 사랑의 행운]
because
왜냐하면
It's you?
당신이에요?
what happened?
무슨 일이야?
I think you are disappointed to see me.
당신이 나를 보고 매우 실망한 것 같아요 .
Gosh, that's not it, is it?
맙소사, 그런 건 아니지?
Can I exchange it for another one?
다른 것으로 바꿀 수 있나요?
please.
제발.
Change who? Change what?
누구를 바꾸시겠습니까? 뭘 바꿔?
Change my luck in love.
내 행운을 사랑으로 바꾸세요.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
what you up to?
무엇을 하려고 하시나요?
It's getting colder.
추워지고있다.
I'm worried you might catch a cold.
감기에 걸릴까 봐 걱정이에요.
Don't do that. I do not like you.
그거 하지마. 나는 너를 좋아하지 않아.
What if I want to like you?
내가 당신을 좋아하고 싶다면?
Build bridges to this sanctuary.
이 대피소에 다리를 놓아라.
Eres tan molesto, Fang Mingfan.
Eres tan Molesto, Fang Mingfan.
what did I do?
내가 뭘 한거지?
You see, according to the astrology,
보세요, 운세에 따르면,
Today I am going to meet my prince.
오늘은 왕자님을 만나러 갑니다.
prince?
왕자?
are you talking about me?
너 나에 대해 말하는 거니?
No, I hope it's not you.
아니, 당신이 아니길 바라요.
Mira.
미라.
A few minutes later,
몇 분 안에,
The New Year's bell is about to ring.
새해의 종소리가 울릴 것입니다.
No one comes here but me .
나 외에는 여기에 올 사람이 아무도 없어요 .
so
그래서
Who accepts destiny .
운명이 준비한 것을 받아들이는 사람 .
what you up to?
무엇을 하려고 하시나요?
they are.
그들은.
If the rope is too tight, it will break.
밧줄이 너무 팽팽하면 끊어질 것이다.
You should allow yourself to enjoy yourself every now and then.
때때로 자신이 조금이라도 즐길 수 있도록 허용해야 합니다 .
Otherwise you will be bored
그렇지 않으면 당신은 매우 지루할 것입니다
Over the years.
몇 년 동안.
not all
전부는 아니다
They still have many years to go.
그들은 그들보다 훨씬 더 많은 시간을 가지고 있습니다.
Life is short.
인생은 짧다.
Some people don't want to waste even a minute.
어떤 사람들은 단 1분도 낭비하고 싶지 않습니다 .
So we must cherish time
그러므로 우리는 시간을 소중히 여겨야 한다
And enjoy the moment.
그리고 현재를 즐겨라.
Lunar New Year's eve
새해 전날
This is the time to say goodbye and welcome something new.
이제 작별 인사를 하고 새로운 것을 맞이할 시간입니다 .
Death is a farewell and a beginning.
죽음은 이별 이자 시작이다.
Thank you all for being here tonight
오늘 밤 여기에 와주신 모든 분들께 감사드립니다
at my farewell party
내 송별회에서
On this special night.
이 특별한 밤에.
I live a life of fighting.
나는 전쟁의 삶을 살아왔습니다.
A rocket broke my leg bone.
포병 로켓으로 인해 다리뼈가 부러졌습니다.
But luckily, I survived.
하지만 다행스럽게도 나는 살아 남았습니다.
To be alive is a victory.
살아 있는 것이 승리입니다.
In my final battle,
내 마지막 전투에서,
I have encountered my most ferocious enemy.
나는 나의 가장 사나운 적을 만났다.
Although Dr. Gu Yunzheng of Friendship Hospital
우호병원의 구윤정 박사는
Help me find this enemy,
내가 이 적을 찾는 데 도움을 줬어요
This time I wasn't so lucky.
이번에는 운이 좋지 않았습니다.
The tumor is malignant
종양은 악성이다
It doesn’t take long for it to spread throughout my brain.
그리고 곧 그것은 내 뇌 전체에 퍼질 것입니다.
I want to shoot him right now
지금 당장 그를 쏘고 싶습니다.
But I can't just leave.
하지만 이대로는 떠날 수 없어요.
I like a Chinese saying very much.
나는 중국에서 쓰는 말을 좋아한다.
When life is at its best,
인생이 가장 좋을 때,
You have to enjoy happiness to the fullest.
기쁨을 마음껏 누려야 합니다.
I, Kuyat, am not afraid of death.
나 쿠야테는 죽는 것이 두렵지 않다.
What I fear is that I have never lived.
내가 두려워하는 것은 내가 살아본 적이 없다는 것이다.
Tomorrow I will keep fighting, I will keep hunting,
내일도 계속 싸우고, 사냥을 계속하고,
Like the first day I picked up a gun.
첫날처럼 총을 집어 들었습니다.
I will make a grand appearance without any regrets .
후회 없이 멋진 데뷔를 할게요 .
I did not come to this life in vain.
나는 이 삶에 헛되이 들어온 것이 아닙니다.
This is the farewell party I want
이게 내가 원하는 송별회 야
No tears, just joy.
눈물은 없고 기쁨만 있을 뿐입니다.
(I will enter in a gorgeous way and leave no regrets.)
(후회없이 화려하게 입장하겠습니다 .)
(I did not come to this life in vain.)
(나는 이생에 헛되이 온 것이 아니다.)
There is a custom in Lakaya.
Lakaya에는 관습이 있습니다.
When the New Year's bell rings,
새해의 종이 울리면 ,
Kissing those around you will bring good luck throughout the year.
옆 사람과 키스하면 한 해 동안 행운이 찾아올 것입니다.
Let's hug each other tightly and have a passionate kiss!
서로 꼭 끌어안고 열정적인 키스를 해보세요!
♪Your secret♪
♪너 비밀♪
♪Luckily, I hear all your dreams♪
♪다행히도 너의 꿈은 다 들려♪
♪Come closer, I can feel the curve of your smile♪
♪가까이 와라 너의 미소의 곡선이 느껴져♪
♪This is an extension of happiness♪
♪행복의 연장입니다♪
♪ again and again ♪
♪몇번이고 또♪
♪My secret♪
♪미 비밀♪
♪I have forgotten that I was once an island♪
♪내가 한때 외로운 섬이었다는 사실을 벌써 잊어버렸어요♪
♪I've been waiting for this moment for a long time♪
♪ 오랫동안 이 순간을 기다렸어요 ♪
♪I will dream about you again♪
♪다시 한번 당신의 꿈을 꾸게 될 것입니다♪
You said you don't like me, right?
내가 싫다고 했지?
I... need a favor from you.
난... 당신의 부탁이 필요해요.
Elliot tried to kiss me earlier, didn't you see?
엘리엇이 아까 나한테 키스하려고 했는데, 못 보셨나요?
did you ever forcefully kiss me
나한테 억지로 키스한 거야?
To stop you from kissing Elliot?
엘리엇에게 키스하는 걸 막으라고요?
because?
왜냐하면?
you always thought Elliot
당신은 항상 엘리엇이
He's handsome, isn't he?
그 사람 정말 잘생겼지, 그렇지?
Forced kiss?
강제 키스?
Why do you have so many questions?
왜 이렇게 질문이 많아요?
You do not want it?
당신은 의지가 없습니까?
You say you don't want to
입으로 하기 싫다고 하던데요.
But your body looks genuine.
그런데 네 몸은 진심인 것 같아.
Jiang Muying.
장무잉.
You must share the responsibility with me.
당신은 나와 함께 책임을 져야합니다.
♪Your secret♪
♪너 비밀♪
♪Luckily, I hear all your dreams♪
♪다행히도 너의 꿈은 다 들려♪
♪Come closer, I can feel the curve of your smile♪
♪가까이 와라 너의 미소의 곡선이 느껴져♪
♪This is an extension of happiness♪
♪행복의 연장입니다♪
♪ again and again ♪
♪몇번이고 또♪
♪My secret♪
♪미 비밀♪
♪I have forgotten that I was once an island♪
♪내가 한때 외로운 섬이었다는 사실을 벌써 잊어버렸어요♪
♪I've been waiting for this moment for a long time♪
♪ 오랫동안 이 순간을 기다렸어요 ♪
♪I will dream about you again♪
♪다시 한번 당신의 꿈을 꾸게 될 것입니다♪
(Su Wei'an.)
(소웨이안.)
(what's on your mind?)
(무슨 생각을 하고 있나요?)
(Do you have the right to fall in love?)
(당신에게는 사랑에 빠질 권리가 있나요?)
(Why should I kiss him?)
(내가 왜 그 사람에게 키스해야 하는데?)
(That idiot really took advantage of me.)
(그 바보는 정말 나를 이용했다.)
【Gimhae City】 You have a stomach problem.
[진하이시] 위장에 문제가 있으신데요.
Even if the company encounters financing problems,
회사가 자금조달에 어려움을 겪더라도
If you are looking for investment,
투자처를 찾고 계시다면,
You shouldn't drink so much.
술을 너무 많이 마시면 ​​안 됩니다.
Agua.
아구아.
Thanks.
그라시아스.
If Principal Xu
만약 쉬 회장이
It can indeed bring us new funds,
우리에게 새로운 자금을 가져다 줄 수 있습니다.
Financial pressure for HDQ39 development
HDQ39 개발에 대한 재정적 압박
will decrease.
감소할 것입니다.
I will follow the progress of my father's work.
나는 아버지의 사업이 어떻게 진행되는지 지켜볼 것입니다 .
Don't worry too much.
너무 걱정하지 마세요.
but i don't want to
하지만 나는 원하지 않는다
I see you working so hard in the future.
앞으로도 열심히 노력하는 모습을 볼게요.
Of course.
란.
Thank you for always sharing my burden.
항상 저에게 부담을 나눠주셔서 감사합니다.
tonight
오늘 밤
I will go to your house.
나는 당신의 집에 갈 것이다.
You drank a lot,
당신은 술을 많이 마셨고,
So I want to take care of you.
그래서 나는 당신을 돌보고 싶습니다.
It's not necessary
필요하지 않습니다.
Yo...
에야디야...
I have other things to do.
다른 할 일이 있어요.
Did Su Wei'an really drop out of school ?
Su Wei'an 은 정말 자퇴한 걸까요 ?
certainly.
물론.
[three years ago]
[3 년 전]
last semester,
지난 학기,
Had a big scandal with her best friend
그녀의 가장 친한 친구와 큰 스캔들을 일으켰다
for authorship.
저자를 위해.
He even denounced his own teacher.
그는 심지어 자신의 선생님을 비난했습니다.
It’s not too much for him to give up his studies in order to become a writer, right?
그가 저자가 되기 위해 학업을 포기하는 것은 지나친 일이 아니죠?
I heard
나는 그것을 들었다
Wen Ran's father
원란의 아버지
Director of the Department of Neurology, Zhanghe Hospital.
장허병원 신경과장이다 .
Su Weian denounced Wen Ran and He Xiaoguang,
Su Wei'an은 Wen Ran과 He Xiaoguang을 비난했습니다.
What's bothering you so much
뭐가 그렇게 귀찮았어?
Go to Zhanghe Hospital and Huaren Hospital.
장허병원(Zhang He Hospital) 과 화렌병원(Huaren Hospital)으로 이동합니다.
Good morning sir.
안녕하세요 선생님.
That person is Mr. Du from the Department of Neurology.
그 분이 신경과 두 선배님이세요.
Director Du's son.
두 감독의 아들.
I remember that he and Su Weian had a good relationship.
나는 그와 Su Wei'an이 꽤 친했던 것을 기억합니다.
In the past, I often saw them together in the laboratory
예전에는 연구실에서 같이 보곤 했는데
and frequent trips to the library.
그리고 도서관에 자주 가요.
[Du Yuncheng] [Wei'an, ¿ abandonaste tus estudios?]
[두윤청] [웨이안, ¿ Tus estudios를 포기하시겠습니까?]
【If you need help, you can come to me at any time. 】
[도움이 필요하시면 언제든지 저에게 오세요.]
[Will Huntington's disease gene carriers develop Huntington's disease? 】
[ 헌팅턴병 유전자의 보인자가 헌팅턴병을 발병하게 됩니까?]
Huntington's disease?
헌팅턴 병?
(Su Weian dropped out of school .)
(Su Wei'an은 학업을 중간에 포기했습니다.)
(Why are you looking for information about Huntington’s disease?)
( 헌팅턴병에 대한 정보를 찾는 이유는 무엇입니까 ?)
Yuncheng.
윈청.
I asked
나는 물었다
All medical universities in Paris.
파리의 모든 의과 대학 에서
None of them have a student named Su Weian.
그들 중 Su Wei'an이라는 학생은 없습니다 .
Her mother said she went to Paris to study.
그녀의 어머니는 그녀가 파리로 공부하러 갔다고 말했습니다 .
Keep looking for her.
그녀를 계속 찾아보세요.
used to be
였다
Go to some unknown university?
잘 알려지지 않은 대학에?
impossible.
불가능한.
His grades are very good.
그는 매우 좋은 성적을 받았습니다.
He did get into a top university.
그는 확실히 일류 대학에 입학했습니다.
Well, I'll keep looking.
글쎄요, 계속해서 찾아보겠습니다.
[Vian, where are you? 】
[웨이안, 어디야?]
【Resignation report】
[사임보고]
[library]
[도서관]
Hello Professor Wen.
안녕하세요, 원교수님.
I am Du Yuncheng, the project manager of Jiehui Pharmaceutical.
저는 Jiehui Pharmaceutical의 프로젝트 매니저 Du Yuncheng입니다.
You go first, I'll be right there.
너 먼저 가, 나도 바로 갈게.
Are you the son of Director Du Yongsong of Huaren Hospital?
화인병원 두용송 원장의 아들이시죠 ?
do you know me?
저를 아시나요?
My daughter talked about you.
내 딸이 당신에 대해 이야기했습니다.
He said you are his senior.
당신이 선배라고 하더군요.
Because you are looking for me?
나를 찾기 때문에?
Professor Wen.
원 교수님.
I speak on behalf of Jiehui Pharmaceutical
저는 Jiehui Pharmaceuticals를 대표하여 말씀드리고 싶습니다.
About the development of the reactivating drug HDQ39
HDQ39 신약 개발 재개에 대해
For Huntington's disease.
헌팅턴병의 경우.
Are you sure you want to invest?
투자하시겠습니까?
In the HDQ39 project?
HDQ39 프로젝트에서요?
What you should know about Huntington’s disease
헌팅턴병을 알아야 합니다.
Extremely rare in the world.
세계적으로는 극히 드뭅니다.
[Library] (Global incidence no.)
[도서관] (글로벌 발생률은 그렇지 않습니다)
(More than 3/10,000. The number of patients in China is less than 3,000.)
(3/10,000을 초과합니다. 중국의 환자 수는 3,000명 미만입니다.)
(Why invest in research)
(왜 연구에 투자하고 싶나요 ?)
(A drug to treat this rare disease?)
( 이런 희귀병에 대한 약이요 ?)
(This medicine makes sense to me.)
(이 약은 나에게 매우 의미가 있습니다.)
(I have important reasons to investigate it.)
(나는 그것을 조사해야 할 중요한 이유가 있습니다 .)
(Wei'an.)
(웨이안.)
(If HDQ39 is developed successfully)
(HDQ39가 개발에 성공할 경우 )
(And brings hope for Huntington's disease,)
(그리고 헌팅턴병에 대한 희망을 제공합니다.)
(Can you come back?)
(돌아오실 수 있나요?)
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
Your son has
당신의 아들은
Subarachnoid hemorrhage.
지주막 하 출혈.
That?
저것?
what are you saying?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Subarachnoid hemorrhage.
지주막 하 출혈.
Do you have a tumor on your head?
머리에 종양이 생겼나요?
No
아니요
You worry.
당신은 걱정합니다.
You say this is not a problem?
문제가 없다고 하던데요?
That? this?
저것? 이것?
here.
여기.
I do not understand.
모르겠어요.
I see.
이해합니다.
you do not know.
넌 몰라.
I know.
알아요.
No, I still don't understand.
아니요, 아직도 이해가 안 돼요.
Miss.
숙녀.
return
돌아오다
here
여기
this afternoon.
오늘 오후.
The translator will be here by then.
그러면 번역가들이 여기에 있을 것입니다.
OK?
좋아요?
OK
좋아요.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Where are those two translators?
그 두 번역가는 어디에 있나요?
Why hasn’t Su Wei’an come yet?
왜 Su Wei'an은 아직 도착하지 않았나요?
You should ask yourself.
스스로에게 물어보세요.
boss.
사장.
What did you do yesterday?
어제 무엇을 했나요?
Al...
에이어...
Bring Su Wei'an,
여기 Su Wei'an을 데려가세요.
Come for consultation.
상담에.
It's not Su Wei'an's turn to work today.
오늘은 Su Wei'an의 출근 차례가 아닙니다.
You kissed her forcefully last night.
당신은 어젯밤에 그녀에게 강제로 키스했습니다.
Can't she avoid you for a few days?
그녀가 며칠 동안 당신을 피할 수는 없나요?
Then, bring Jiang Muying here.
그럼 Jiang Muying을 여기로 데려가세요.
Or you call her.
아니면 그녀에게 전화하세요.
I've already called him. no answer.
나는 그에게 전화했습니다. 대답하지 않습니다.
What happened between you?
당신 사이에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있나요?
She forcefully kissed me last night.
어젯밤에 그녀는 나에게 강제로 키스했다.
Can't she avoid you for a few days?
그녀가 며칠 동안 당신을 피할 수는 없나요?
what's on your mind?
당신은 무엇을 생각하고 있습니까?
Boss, I was forcefully kissed.
사장님, 제가 강제로 키스를 했어요.
Don't you care about me at all?
나한테는 별로 관심이 없어?
I can be a little worried about you.
나는 당신에 대해 조금 걱정할 수 있습니다.
Why was it so sudden last night?
어젯밤에 갑자기 왜?
Did you kiss Translator Su?
번역가 Su에게 키스하셨나요?
Are you interested in her?
당신은 그녀에게 관심이 있나요?
Have you checked all the rooms?
방은 다 확인하셨나요?
they are.
그들은.
Good morning darling.
좋은 아침 사랑.
The French are really romantics.
프랑스인들은 정말 낭만주의자들이다.
Not long ago, he came here to pursue Su Translation.
얼마 전 그는 수 번역가를 찾으러 이곳에 왔습니다.
uncle?
삼촌?
Who did he call uncle?
그 사람이 누구에게 삼촌이라고 불렀나요?
"Couchou" means "honey"
슈슈는 꿀이라는 뜻이에요
French.
프랑스어.
You are my dear too.
당신은 또한 나의 사랑입니다.
this is life.
이것이 삶이다.
Whatever you want to know, I will tell you.
당신이 알고 싶은 것이라면 무엇이든 말해줄게요.
You said there is progress in research.
연구에 진전이 있다고 말씀하셨습니다 .
Has the drug passed animal testing?
약이 동물 실험을 통과했나요 ?
Huntington's disease?
헌팅턴병 때문에?
These are data from Henri Mondo's laboratory
Henri Mondo 연구소의 데이터입니다.
My mentor sent this to me today.
오늘 선생님이 보내주신 것이에요.
I'll print a copy for you.
사본을 인쇄해 드리겠습니다.
Thanks.
그라시아스.
[Cellular and Molecular Neurobiology]
[세포분자신경생물학]
We received complaints from doctors at the hospital
병원 의사로부터 불만사항을 접수받았습니다
The man illegally occupied the space,
이 사람이 불법적으로 그 공간을 점유했다는 것,
Bringing uninspected food
검열되지 않은 음식을 가져왔다
Seriously affecting work order and environmental sanitation.
작업 순서와 환경 위생에 심각한 영향을 미쳤습니다 .
Translator Su asked him to leave temporarily.
수 번역가님, 잠시 자리를 비워달라고 부탁하세요 .
complaint?
불만?
We are outdoors.
우리는 야외에 있습니다.
we often drink coffee
우리는 커피를 자주 마신다.
We eat sandwiches here.
그리고 우리는 여기서 샌드위치를 ​​먹습니다.
Who files a complaint?
누가 불만을 제기했나요?
Let’s talk somewhere else.
대화 장소를 바꾸자.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I will return to Paris next month.
다음 달에 나는 파리로 돌아갈 것이다.
Do you want to go to Henri Mondor's laboratory?
앙리 몬도르 연구실에 가보실래요 ?
Can you take me to see Dr. Marta?
저를 마르타 박사님에게 데려가 주시겠어요?
Not just a visit.
그냥 방문하는 것이 아닙니다.
I'm asking you,
나는 당신에게 묻고 있습니다.
Would you like to work in Henri Mondor's laboratory?
Henri Mondor 연구실에서 일하고 싶나요 ?
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
You will be able to work with Dr. Marta.
당신은 Dr. Marta와 함께 일할 수 있을 것입니다.
Will you go to Paris with me?
저와 함께 파리에 가실래요?
Can I participate in Huntington's disease research?
헌팅턴병 연구 에 참여할 수 있나요 ?
but I...
하지만 난...
I only have a bachelor's degree from China Medical University.
저는 중국 의과대학에서 학사 학위만 받았습니다 .
Is this acceptable?
그게 받아들여질 수 있나요?
I checked it out specifically.
구체적으로 확인해봤습니다.
In France, degrees from Huaren Medical University are recognized.
프랑스에서는 Huaren 의과대학의 학위가 인정됩니다 .
In Dr. Marta's laboratory,
마르타 박사의 연구실에서는
There are research assistants with a bachelor's degree.
학사 학위를 가진 연구 조교가있었습니다 .
¡ Amiable!
온화한!
great!
엄청난!
But you have to be prepared.
하지만 준비가 되어 있어야 합니다.
Huntington's disease is very rare.
헌팅턴병은 매우 드뭅니다.
Research on new drugs will be a long-term endeavor.
신약 연구는 장기적인 일이 될 것입니다.
who knows,
누가 알아,
You may have to stay in Paris for many years.
당신은 수년 동안 파리에 머물러야 할 수도 있습니다 .
no problem.
괜찮아요.
I would do anything if Huntington's disease could be cured .
헌팅턴병을 치료할 수 있다면 나는 무엇이든 할 것입니다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
come over.
이리 오세요.
You leave during work hours.
당신은 근무 시간 중에 떠나고 있었습니다.
I told you
내가 말했잖아
What are the consequences of leaving your position, remember?
당신의 자리를 떠나면 어떤 결과가 생길까요 , 기억하시나요?
I have to rest today.
오늘은 좀 쉬어야 해요.
It was Jiang's turn to go to work.
이제 Jiang이 일할 차례입니다.
Besides, Jiang can handle it himself now.
게다가 Jiang은 이제 스스로를 다룰 수 있게 되었습니다.
Yes, she did a great job.
네, 그녀는 아주 잘 해냈습니다.
Intracranial aneurysm removal
두개내 동맥류 의 번역을 제외하고
as an intracranial tumor
두개내종양으로서
and cerebral arterial malformations such as cerebral arterial adhesion,
뇌동맥 유착 등의 뇌동맥 기형 ,
Other translations are acceptable.
다른 번역은 허용되었습니다.
At least in comparison
적어도 비교하면
And those who fall in love during working hours,
근무시간에 연애를 하는 사람들과
She is more responsible.
그녀는 좀 더 책임감이 있습니다.
Who are you implying?
누구를 암시하는 겁니까?
Who takes up work time to fall in love?
연애를 위해 근무 시간을 빼앗는 사람은 누구인가?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
french man
프랑스 남자
They have always been known for their pursuit of romance and novelty.
그들은 항상 낭만적이고 소설적인 것을 추구하는 것으로 알려져 왔습니다 .
They can speak sweet words effortlessly.
그들은 쉽게 달콤한 말을 할 수 있습니다.
You shouldn't take it seriously.
심각하게 받아들이면 안됩니다.
I just want to remember you.
나는 단지 당신을 기억하고 싶습니다.
Don't be anxious about love,
사랑에 서두르지 마세요.
Lest your dreams be shattered and your work affected.
당신의 달콤한 꿈이 깨지는 것을 방지하여 당신의 일이 영향을 받게 될 것입니다.
Professor Gu, don't worry.
구교수님, 걱정하지 마세요.
As a temporary translator,
임시 번역가로서,
I won't cause any problems
난 아무 문제도 일으키지 않을 거야
to the medical team.
의료진에게.
That was not what I meant.
그건 나의 의도가 아니 었어.
That's what I mean.
이것이 내가 의미하는 바입니다.
And, in the future, this situation will never happen again.
그리고 앞으로는 이런 상황이 다시는 발생하지 않을 것입니다.
I'm resigning.
그만 두겠습니다.
give up?
포기하다?
Espera, Su Wei'an.
에스페라, 수웨이안.
I'm just reminding you.
나는 단지 당신에게 상기시켜 주었을 뿐입니다.
You don't need to get angry and quit.
화를 내고 그만 둘 필요는 없습니다 .
I'm not angry.
난 화나지 않았어.
This is a carefully considered decision.
잘 생각한 결정입니다.
Was it because of that kiss?
그 키스 때문인가?
Yo...
에야디야...
There's no need to take it so seriously.
그렇게 심각하게 받아들일 필요는 없습니다.
that kiss
그 키스
This is just a local New Year custom.
그것은 단지 지역 의 새해 풍습 이었습니다.
you are close
당신은 가까웠어요
At that time, so I...
그때는 그래서 내가...
You...shouldn't take it seriously.
당신은… 심각하게 받아들여서는 안 됩니다.
Professor Gu, there is no need to remind me about this.
구교수님, 그걸 나한테 상기시켜줄 필요는 없어요.
It's just a kiss.
그것은 단지 키스였습니다.
Of course I don't take it seriously.
물론 심각하게 받아들이지는 않습니다.
so,
그래서,
Why did you resign?
왜 사임합니까?
for money.
돈을 위해.
I found a more lucrative job.
나는 더 수익성이 좋은 직업을 찾았습니다.
I'm leaving here and going to Paris.
나는 여기 파리로 떠난다.
So please,
그러니 제발,
Don't get in my way of making money.
내가 돈 버는 걸 방해하지 마세요 .
♪Olvida is not important♪
♪올비다르는 중요하지 않아요♪
♪You are the one who gives me courage♪
♪나에게 용기를 주는 사람은 당신이에요♪
♪Scenery you will never see♪
♪한번도 볼 수 없는 풍경♪
♪I wish you all the best♪
♪당신의 행운을 기원합니다♪
♪Olvida is not important♪
♪올비다르는 중요하지 않아요♪
♪I am the one who saved me♪
♪나를 구하는 건 바로 나야♪
♪Siempre te amaré♪
♪Siempre te amare♪
♪Nunca me rindo♪
♪눈카 미 린도♪
Are you going to France?
프랑스에 갈 건가요?
So suddenly?
그럼 갑자기?
Suddenly I received a big order.
갑자기 큰 주문을 받았습니다.
I have to go there.
나는 거기에 가야만 한다.
I'm going to Paris.
나는 파리에 갈 예정이다.
All right.
괜찮은.
Wherever you go, take me with you.
어디를 가든지 나를 데리고 가세요.
OK?
좋아요?
Jiang.
장.
If you follow me, you'll just be at a loss
저를 따라오시면 그냥 압도당하실 거에요.
And you don't need money.
그리고 돈은 필요하지 않습니다.
listen to me. Go home quickly.
내 말을 들어보세요. 곧 집에 오세요.
No.
아니요.
I came all the way here just to find you.
나는 당신을 찾으러 지금까지 왔습니다.
You can't leave me alone anymore.
당신은 나를 다시 혼자 내버려 둘 수 없습니다.
never.
안 돼요.
Plus, I've never been to Paris.
게다가 나는 파리에 가본 적도 없다.
Take me with you.
나를 데리고 가세요.
Are you really going to leave me alone and go away?
정말 나를 내버려두고 혼자 갈 생각인가요 ?
listen. impossible.
듣다. 불가능한.
Three years ago, I didn't see it coming.
3년 전만 해도 그런 일이 일어날 줄은 몰랐습니다.
But this time,
하지만 이번에는
I won't let you go alone.
나는 당신을 혼자 보내지 않을 것입니다.
Otherwise, please let me know.
그렇지 않으면 말해 보세요.
Because you're leaving? where are you going? How long will you stay there?
당신이 떠나기 때문에? 어디 가세요? 거기 얼마나 오래 머물 예정인가요?
and,
그리고 또한,
Why did you suddenly give up your studies?
왜 그렇게 갑자기 학업을 포기하셨나요 ?
Why did you give up your dream of becoming a doctor?
의사의 꿈을 포기한 이유는 무엇인가요 ?
You have to explain all this to me clearly.
이 모든 것에 대해 나에게 명확하게 설명해야 합니다 .
Yo...
에야디야...
I'm going to run away with Elliot
나는 엘리엇과 함께 도망칠 거예요.
Escape?
탈출하다?
precise.
정확한.
So, Jiang, you can't follow me.
그러니 장 씨, 당신은 나를 따라갈 수 없습니다.
Are you going to elope with Elliot?
엘리엇과 함께 도망갈 건가요?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
I know you like Gu Yunzheng.
나는 당신이 Gu Yunzheng을 좋아한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
You can hide it from others,
다른 사람에게 숨길 수도 있고,
But not me.
하지만 나한테는 아니야.
You 've liked him since you were in college, right?
너 대학때 그 사람 좋아했지?
And, you two kissed at that New Year's party.
게다가 너희 둘은 그 신년회에서 키스를 했어.
now you tell me
이제 당신은 나에게 말해
you want to run away
네가 탈출할 거라고
With a French man you barely know?
잘 알지도 못하는 프랑스 남자랑 ?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
I'm actually not stupid.
나는 정말로 바보가 아니다.
Jiang.
장.
El besoque le di a Gu Yunzheng
El besoque le di a Gu Yunzheng
It's just a New Year gesture
그냥 새해를 맞이하는 몸짓이었는데,
Doesn't have any special meaning.
특별한 의미 없이.
It was love at first sight with Eliot.
엘리엇과의 첫눈에 반한 사랑이었습니다.
He is the love of my life.
그는 내 인생의 사랑입니다.
I'm going to France with him.
나는 그와 함께 프랑스로 갈 예정이다.
and know,
그리고 알아둬,
Love has no logic
사랑에는 논리가 없다
It also doesn't obey orders.
명령에도 따르지 않습니다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
arts.
Ven.
Explain this.
이것을 설명하십시오.
Why do you study euthanasia?
안락사를 연구한 이유는 무엇인가요?
Someone asked me for help before;
예전에 누군가 나에게 도움을 요청했는데,
Promises very high commissions.
매우 높은 수수료를 약속합니다.
The commission is very high.
매우 높은 수수료.
So I saved the files but didn't throw them away.
그래서 나는 이 문서들을 버리지 않고 저장해 두었습니다.
Do you think I want to die?
내가 죽고 싶을 것 같아?
I'm still alive and well.
저는 지금 아주 잘 살아있습니다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Did you tell the truth?
진실을 말한 적이 있나요?
Do you really consider me your friend?
당신은 정말로 나를 친구라고 생각합니까?
you are my best friend.
너는 내 가장 친한 친구 야.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
no matter what happens,
무슨 일이 일어나든,
If you have something painful tormenting you,
당신을 괴롭히는 고통스러운 일이 있다면,
you can tell me.
당신은 나에게 말할 수 있습니다.
I know there are some things you can't tell your mother.
엄마한테 말할 수 없는 게 있다는 걸 알아요 .
But you can tell me.
그러나 당신은 나에게 말할 수 있습니다.
I will definitely keep it a secret.
절대 비밀로 할게요.
Oh, really.
오, 진짜.
Mira.
미라.
I have been coming to Lakaya for a long time.
나는 오랫동안 라카야에 있었습니다.
I haven't revealed anything about you to Mi-ran.
나는 메이란에게 당신에 대해 아무것도 밝히지 않았습니다.
I'm very reliable.
나는 매우 신뢰할 수 있습니다.
And we are like family,
그리고 우리는 가족 같아요.
best friend.
가장 친한 친구.
I can help you share a lot.
나는 당신이 많은 것을 공유하도록 도울 수 있습니다.
Pero, Jiang, yo...
페로, 장, 요...
I did not lie to you.
나는 당신에게 거짓말을 하는 것이 아닙니다.
I'm really going to run away with Elliot
난 정말 엘리엇과 함께 도망칠 거예요.
real.
정말.
And you
당신은요
You want me to find love too, right?
너도 내가 사랑을 찾길 바라셨지?
That amulet in my bag
내 가방에 있던 그 부적,
You put it in, right?
넣으셨죠?
Trust me, Chiang.
날 믿어, 장.
You are so stubborn.
당신은 너무 고집스럽군요.
You went to France without telling me the truth, did you?
당신은 프랑스로 가는데 나에게 진실을 말하지 않는 거죠, 그렇죠?
Bueno.
부에노.
If you leave, our friendship is over.
당신이 떠나면 우리의 우정은 끝나게 됩니다.
I don't need a friend like you.
너같은 친구는 필요없어
Jiang.
장.
I'm resigning.
그만 두겠습니다.
give up?
포기하다?
Was it because of that kiss?
그 키스 때문인가?
There's no need to take it so seriously.
그렇게 심각하게 받아들일 필요는 없습니다.
that kiss
그 키스
This is just a local New Year custom.
그것은 단지 지역 의 새해 풍습 이었습니다.
You were nearby at the time, so I...
그때 네가 친해서 난...
You...shouldn't take it seriously.
당신은… 심각하게 받아들여서는 안 됩니다.
Professor Gu, there is no need to remind me about this.
구교수님, 그걸 나한테 상기시켜줄 필요는 없어요.
It's just a kiss.
그것은 단지 키스였습니다.
French kiss
프렌치 키스
This is as normal as eating or drinking.
이는 물을 먹거나 마시는 것과 마찬가지로 정상적인 현상입니다.
Of course I don't take it seriously.
물론 심각하게 받아들이지는 않습니다.
(Gu Yunzheng.)
(구윤정.)
(You are a wonderful person in every way.)
(당신은 모든 면에서 훌륭한 사람입니다 .)
(Why do you only have that stupid mouth?)
(왜 그 서투른 입만 가지고 있는 걸까요?)
【Friendship Hospital】
[우정병원]
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Have you had breakfast?
벌써 아침을 먹었나요?
No, it's too forced.
아니, 너무 강요적이다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
This is the glutinous rice balls from the canteen.
이곳은 식당의 탕위안이고,
Very sweet and sticky.
매우 달콤하고 끈적합니다.
I bought it for you.
나는 당신을 위해 그것을 샀습니다.
Al,
에이어,
I did not mean that.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었어.
actually, I...
사실은 내가...
No,
아니요,
I said too much.
내가 말을 너무 많이 하고 있구나.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Let's have breakfast together.
아침을 같이 먹자.
you can trust
전적으로 믿으셔도 됩니다
On Dr. Gu’s medical skills.
구 박사의 의술에 대해.
At Huaren Hospital in China,
중국 화렌병원에서는
He is the youngest associate doctor.
그는 최연소 부의사이다.
Although he looks a little reserved
다소 내성적인 것 같긴 하지만
and distant,
그리고 먼,
Very responsible
책임감이 매우 강하다
with every patient.
각 환자와 함께.
So, don't worry.
그러니 걱정하지 마세요.
This operation will definitely be successful.
이번 수술은 반드시 성공할 것입니다.
Genial, Su Wei'an.
상냥한, 수웨이안.
You are so aggressive in front of me.
당신은 내 앞에서 너무 공격적입니다.
But behind my back, you praised me.
그런데 당신은 내 뒤에서 나에 대해 환하게 이야기합니다.
You are hypocritical.
당신은 매우 위선적입니다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
I was just going to find you.
방금 당신을 찾으려고 했어요.
This is for you.
이건 널위한거야.
[Resignation letter] This is my resignation letter.
[사직서] 저의 사직서입니다.
Although this is a temporary job,
비록 임시직이었지만,
I think it should be formal.
공식적으로 해야 할 것 같아요.
I appreciate your time helping me.
당신이 나를 도와준 시간에 감사드립니다.
I hope you find it soon
빨리 찾을 수 있기를 바라요
Leave it to a more qualified translator.
더 자격을 갖춘 번역가에게.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
you have a good command of french
당신은 프랑스어 수준이 좋습니다
and medical history.
그리고 병력.
Find the right translator
적합한 번역가 찾기
soon
곧
not simple.
쉽지 않다.
and
그리고
You want to make money,
당신은 돈을 벌려고 하고,
There is no need to go to France.
프랑스에 갈 필요는 없습니다.
I can give you a raise.
연봉을 올려드릴 수 있어요.
It's not necessary
필요하지 않습니다.
It's not just about money.
단지 돈에 관한 것이 아닙니다.
so give it to me
그러니 나에게 줘
a reason that satisfies me
나를 만족시키는 이유,
Reasons why you should give up on something again
당신이 뭔가를 다시 버리려는 이유
Half.
중간.
You said it's not about money.
돈 문제가 아니라고 하셨습니다.
Are you doing this for Elliot?
엘리엇을 위해서 이러는 건가요?
Do you really like Eliot?
엘리엇을 정말 좋아하시나요?
Is it for him?
그를 위한 것인가?
If there's nothing more to say, I'll leave first.
더 할말 없으면 나 먼저 갈게.
I need to go to the embassy to apply for an emergency visa.
긴급 비자를 처리하기 위해 대사관에 가야 합니다 .
According to our contract,
우리 계약에 따르면,
Resignation must be submitted one week in advance.
사직은 일주일 전에 요청해야 합니다.
The resignation will be effective one week after submission.
사직서는 제출 후 일주일 후에 발효됩니다 .
During this time,
이 기간 동안,
You have to keep working.
계속 일해야 해요.
if you are missing,
누락된 경우,
They will deduct your wages.
그들은 당신의 급여를 공제할 것입니다.
♪Move the hands of the clock at night♪
♪밤은 시계바늘을 움직인다♪
♪The noise gradually replaced the silence♪
♪소음이 점차 침묵을 대체합니다♪
♪Our representative meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 표현합니다♪
♪Embedded night rainbow♪
♪밤의 무지개를 담아♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 건너는 바람♪
♪Everyone is a witness to our past♪
♪모두가 과거의 증인이었어♪
♪No one can escape being lost in the vast world♪
♪ 광활한 세계에서 길을 잃을 수밖에 없는 사람은 없습니다 ♪
♪Looking for the one in a million possibility♪
♪ 백만 가지 가능성 중 하나를 찾고 있습니다 ♪
♪Trapped in this city called destiny♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, I love those who are lost♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 나는 길을 잃은 사람들을 사랑합니다♪
♪Holding a cup to warm the lonely soul♪
♪컵을 들고 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄 수 있게 해주세요♪
♪You shine like a shining star♪
♪당신은 빛나는 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Blink in lonely moments♪
♪외로운 순간에 눈을 깜박인다♪
♪Move the hands of the clock at night♪
♪밤은 시계바늘을 움직인다♪
♪The noise gradually replaced the silence♪
♪소음이 점차 침묵을 대체합니다♪
♪Our representative meeting script♪
♪회의 대본을 표현합니다♪
♪Embedded night rainbow♪
♪밤의 무지개를 담아♪
♪And the wind that passes through the desert♪
♪그리고 사막을 건너는 바람♪
♪Everyone is a witness to our past♪
♪모두가 과거의 증인이었어♪
♪No one can escape being lost in the vast world♪
♪ 광활한 세계에서 길을 잃을 수밖에 없는 사람은 없습니다 ♪
♪Looking for the one in a million possibility♪
♪ 백만 가지 가능성 중 하나를 찾고 있습니다 ♪
♪Trapped in this city called destiny♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀♪
♪But still chasing stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, I love those who are lost♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 나는 길을 잃은 사람들을 사랑합니다♪
♪Holding a cup to warm the lonely soul♪
♪컵을 들고 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 ♪
♪Let me hug your crack♪
♪당신의 균열을 안아줄 수 있게 해주세요♪
♪You shine like a shining star♪
♪당신은 빛나는 별처럼 빛나네요♪
♪Blink in lonely moments♪
♪외로운 순간에 눈을 깜박인다♪